Here it comes. Ready, Ray?
Yes, I'm ready. Come!
After the training...
...comes the protein!
So you're in two clubs at once?
Yeah.
I'm finally here at this academy.
I want to do everything I can.
I see, but it's going to be rough.
Don't worry about me.
I've got this.
Are you serious?
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
Episode 2
The Boy Who Became the World's Strongest Sorcerer
Begins His Practical Exercise
Excuse me!
So you've come.
My name is Ray White!
It seems you want to join our
Environmental Research Club.
The Environmental Research Club!
That means we explore the forests,
the rivers, all the way up
to the glacier regions!
Those who conduct environmental
research are fearless!
People call us...
...hunters!
We do not discriminate against ordinaries.
However, a person with a
weak body or a weak mind
cannot keep up with the
Environmental Research Club.
Kinda scrawny.
Not enough bulk...
Clothes off first!
Then we'll talk!
Yes, sir!
Bulk!
Check out that bulk!
I guess he just looks skinny in clothes!
He's huge! So huge he probably has
to pay property tax on those!
Nice muscles.
They're not just for show, either.
You got them by actually using your body.
I trained in the backwoods forests.
So it's Ray, huh?
You have one of these, right?
You've got keen insight, sir.
A gold hunter license?
An ordinary with a gold?!
Even amongst hunters,
a gold hunter is on another level!
But that makes sense then.
That bulk is serious business!
Outstanding potential.
Ray, become a pillar of the
Environmental Research Club.
It would be my pleasure.
Excuse me!
Oh, my. Ray?
You'd like to join?
Yes.
I am interested in the plants
that are living so powerfully.
Even in the most appalling environment,
you can find a flower.
Even if that's a battlefield.
So you like flowers.
I do.
We don't have any other male members, though.
Are you all right with that?
I have no problem communicating with women.
Well, in that case...
I object!
Dina?
He's obviously set his sights on you!
We can't have a man step
into the flower garden.
The flowers would wither.
Not to mention, this person is an ordinary.
Then, let's do this.
I am delegating Ray's case to Dina.
Me?!
That's right.
If you find that he's
unworthy after your evaluation,
you can reject his application.
U-Understood.
Thank you very much!
Um...
My name is Dina Sera. I'm a third-year.
I look forward to working
with you, Miss Sera.
Harumph!
It's obvious that you'll reveal
your true intentions soon enough!
You're going to prepare this space.
So we're making a new garden.
That's right.
It's nice that the academy
let us use this space,
but it's full of weeds and the
soil isn't workable yet, either.
We've got a long way to go.
So is this my entrance test for the club?
You've got one week.
And you've got to do it all by yourself.
Understood.
Good luck, then.
Not that luck will help.
All right.
Shall we begin?
This is looking good.
You've been working really hard.
This is delicious!
I'm glad.
I really love these fruit sandwiches,
so I negotiated with the school
so we could have them.
It's possible to do something like that?
Well, I am the student council president.
You're from the top three families
and the student council president.
You are really amazing.
If you ever have any questions,
you can come to me.
Right, Magic Chevalier is coming up soon.
Magic Chevalier?
It's a competition to find the
strongest magic sword-fighter.
The strongest... you said?
You're not going to participate?
I'll think about it.
Stare...
Rebecca?
Do you mind if I touch them a little?
Go ahead.
Very well.
Wow!
So hard!
Your biceps have an excellent
shape and substance!
I trained in the backwoods forests.
That's amazing!
This is the first time I've
touched a man's muscles.
It's really educational!
Isn't that the Withered?
I wonder if Lady Amelia alone is not enough,
so that's why he's trying to friendly with
Rebecca from the top three noble families.
Typical, perverted mindset of an ordinary.
How did I do, Miss Sera?
...sed.
Huh?
You passed!
Thank you so much!
Then, let's plant some new flowers here.
Yes!
Ray. I have something I'd like you to do.
Let me have a look.
A spy from the empire inside the kingdom?
That is correct.
There is a chance that even this
academy has been infiltrated.
The staff has already been informed as well,
but if you find anything, let me know.
Yes, ma'am.
I apologize.
But the state of affairs in the
kingdom is quite messy right now.
I'd like to resolve this
in secret, if possible.
Claris, is that you?
Ray?
Why would you suddenly talk to
me like that? You startled me!
I apologize for that.
But what are you doing here,
crouched down like that?
I was watching some pill bugs.
Pill bugs?
I know it's weird for a high-class noble
family's daughter to like insects.
Everyone else likes dogs or cats
or some kind of cute animal.
That's why I don't have a lot of friends.
But that's part of who you are.
I think that's really fantastic.
You don't think it's weird?
I said I like bugs!
I like bugs too.
It is a great honor to be your friend.
F-friend?
D-d-d-did you s-say we're f-f-friends?!
I'm sorry.
Somehow it seemed like we
can talk so comfortably,
so maybe I read into it too far.
Did I offend you?
A friend? I've never had...
I mean, if you want to. I guess.
Really? That would be nice.
All right! My very first friend!
I actually made a friend!
What's wrong?
Nothing at all!
I see.
The sun's already starting to go down,
but I'd love to talk about the various
bugs I saw in the jungle some time.
In great detail, you hear!
Promise!
It's a promise.
Besides, talking to you is a lot of fun.
I guess I have no choice.
Since you insist, I'll go along with it.
See you later.
I'm looking forward to it.
Today, we'll be talking about
the derivations of sorcery.
This topic is quite technical,
but is there anyone who
can give an explanation?
Ray White.
How about you give it a try?
Yes, ma'am.
Sorcery is primarily
categorized as low-grade,
mid-grade, high-grade, and holy-grade.
Furthermore: as quick,
remote,
chain,
delay,
material shift,
extensive,
extensive chain.
The aforementioned are
the seven derivations.
White is absolutely right.
You've been studying hard.
Thank you.
That is all for today.
Also, we'll be doing our practical
exercise out in the Kafka Forest.
I want you to form groups
of four before then.
That is all.
Yeah! For us that's easy!
Right, Al?
Lady Rose, will you be in our group?
Please, won't you?
What about being in our group?
What should I do?
Let's group up, Ray.
Is that okay?
It's common knowledge that
I'm not great at sorcery.
You're good at using your body, right?
Besides, a gold hunter
is worth 100 people.
Really? Well, thank you.
But what about the other spots?
Ray?
Elisa, want to be in our group?
But... I mean...
I'm happy, but I'm so physically
weak that I'd just be a burden.
Elisa...
Elisa, let's all do our best together.
We need you.
Ray.
I'll be supporting, too.
Okay. Thank you. Both of you.
Do you still have an open spot?
Of course.
Your spot was there
from the beginning.
Let's go over the details of
this drill one more time.
The aim of this drill is to reach the
goal in the center of the forest.
Do not forget to hit each checkpoint
that are placed throughout the area.
The number stamps you collect
will affect your final scores.
You have 24 hours.
Anything after that will not count.
The Kafka Forest is full of monsters that
this unique environment has nurtured.
Be aware that combat will be necessary.
This will be the first practical
exercise, but do not ask for help.
That might lead to being held back a year.
That is all.
Wait at the designated area until
the signal to start is given.
I'm so nervous.
Don't worry, Elisa.
We're all here with you.
You're so kind.
You don't look nervous at all.
Of course.
If anything, it's a nostalgic feeling.
Nostalgic?
I came from the middle of nowhere,
so I'm used to running around
the forests and the mountains.
Hey, what should we do about our order?
Right, we haven't decided that yet.
Maybe Ray and you should be the vanguard.
I'll be in the middle and
Elisa brings up the rear.
That sounds good.
No, I'd like to take care
of the middle, and help out as needed.
Huh?
I am used to these types of drills,
so I'd like you and Evi to be the vanguard.
That's fine, but what do you mean,
you're used to these types of drills?
Let's just say, I learned a lot
in those backwoods forests.
It's time.
The practical exercise will now commence.
You all ready?
Sure am!
You bet!
I'll do my best.
I will do my best!
The exercise begins now!
Elisa, are you all right?
Ray!
All right!
So this is one of those monsters.
Wow.
Split in two in one hit...
That's amazing. Ray!
Let's go.
Hey, we found a stamp!
Slap that on!
All right!
We're doing great.
Are we even going the right way?
We are, I think...
Are you sure?
That's so huge!
We're making really good time.
At this rate, we could
even make it back first.
Ray was really amazing.
He was.
His battle abilities are exceptional.
And he even has a wealth
of survival knowledge.
That's what I'd expect from a gold hunter.
I came across many a monster
in those backwoods forests.
So I'm used to this kind of situation.
Backwoods forests, huh?
She's doubting the "Universally applicable
theorem of the backwoods forest"?
Master, you promised something else...
You're something different, huh Ray?
So are you, for that matter.
I would've never expected the eldest daughter
of the Rose family to align
herself with an ordinary.
It's beyond weird.
I don't like that bloodline and class stuff.
The Rose family is the leader of the
three big noble families, right?
Aren't you proud of that?
I hate all of that formality.
I mean, I've put in so much effort
to become who I am right now.
Amelia?
It's fine.
I'm really enjoying hanging out with
you because you interact with me
without all that formality.
I'm also happy that we're
getting to know each other.
You really are too cute.
Cute all over!
Amelia, this is getting weird.
We're counting on you, Ray.
Compared to the battlefield,
this forest is heaven.
Is it really okay for me to be here?
Do I have the right to
enjoy this kind of life?
Ray?
Is something wrong?
No.
Let's get ready for tomorrow and go to bed.
Ray, I won't tell you to keep your
identity hidden at all costs forever.
But your situation is quite special.
If you want to enjoy a
normal life at school,
it will be probably best to
try to keep it under wraps.
However, if you ever find some friends
that you can absolutely trust...
What should I do?
Master...
What was that?
A scream?
Hey!
Ray, wait!
I'm sorry, I'm going ahead!
That scream just now. I have a bad feeling.
Help me!
Stay back!
D-Damn it.
What the hell is going on?!
Mister Alium!
Allow me to assist!
Withered?
Inside code, inertial control!
How is he moving like that?
Can you stand, Mister Alium?
Don't you dare look down on me!
You're just an ordinary!
I could've done that all by myself!
Oh, I see.
Did you have some kind of secret strategy?
You bastard!
Ray!
What is that?
What a huge monster.
Mister Alium's party got attacked.
Will you hurry up and get us down from here?
This hurts!
Hurry up!
Elisa, could I ask you to look after them?
Yes, I got it!
I'll help, too.
Did you defeat that by yourself?
Yes, why?
Ray... who are you?
Hey, hey...
This can't be.
Wha...
The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World
~ Next Episode Preview ~
Hey! It's the preview for the next episode
of "The Iceblade Sorcerer
Shall Rule the World"!
Ray faces off against this massive monster!
Can he defeat it and finish this
insane practical exercise in one piece?!
The boy who became the world's
strongest sorcerer enjoys a day off!
Episode 3
The Boy Who Became the World's
Strongest Sorcerer Enjoys a Day Off
Evi Armstrong, signing off!